http://www.libertyfirstcu.com/privacy-policy

Main Menu
How can we help you?
Login
Forgot Password? | First Time User?
Download the Mobile App
Apple
Android
×Close Login
Our offices will be closed Monday, October 12th in observance of Columbus Day.
Please note, local authorities require all individuals inside a venue to wear a mask.  It is our expectation you follow the local guidelines.
×Close alert.
Toggle Menu
Login
Search
How can we help you?
Password
Forgot Password? | First Time User?
Effective January 1, 2019
Trust has always been the foundation of our relationship with members. Because you trust us with your financial and other personal information, we are committed to respect your privacy and safeguard that information. To preserve your trust, we pledge to protect your privacy by adhering to the practices described below. In this Agreement the terms "we," "our," or "us" means Liberty First Credit Union; and the terms "you" or "your" means all members, consumers, borrowers, and guarantors.
Note: By signing any application or agreement with us, or your use or continued use of any of our services, you jointly and severally agree to the terms and conditions set forth in this Policy and Agreement.
Information That We Collect About You. We only collect information about our members for lawful business purposes, or as otherwise required by applicable law. We maintain strict security procedures to protect your information. We collect information about members from the following sources:
Applications for services, verifications, current and past employers, other forms and any communications you send to us including electronic messages from which we collect your name, addresses, phone numbers, social security numbers, driver's license numbers, financial data, birth date, gender and other information.
Transactions involving your accounts or services with us from which we collect information such as your name, account number, balance, payment history, parties to your transactions and card usage.
Consumer Credit Reports from which we collect information regarding your creditworthiness, credit history and account activity .
Market Research Firms that provide us with a variety of information regarding our members such as the number of individuals in a household or home ownership.
You agree that the telephone numbers, street, and E-mail addresses provided in your Membership Agreement and Signature Card, or any other application or communication sent to us are publicly available and may be used to provide notices, disclosures, statements, other communications (including but not limited to our responses to your E-mail communications) and offers for certain products or services.Our web site: Use of our web site or linking to a site we sponsor requires the use of "cookies," which are small pieces of information a web site stores on a visitor's web browser. We do not store confidential or sensitive information through the use of cookies. Our use of cookies enhances our member's online transactions and eases navigation through our web site. For certain applications, such as Access Online, cookies are required to help protect the privacy of a member's transactions by, for example, terminating the session if the member forgets to log out. We use E-mail addresses from members who request electronic services, and from users of our web site who choose to provide their addresses.
Categories of Information We Disclose. To benefit our members, we share the information described in Paragraph 1 above within the Credit Union, which includes all employees, directors, committee members, and with certain trusted third parties described in this paragraph, who are obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of your private information. We use the services of various third parties to assist us in offering financial services to our members. For example, we use the services of third parties for check printing, statement printing, consultant and business development services, processing or facilitating transactions via credit cards, checks, debit cards and other access devices including Access Online or bill pay; for assistance in making loans, or loan underwriting; processing loan applications; appraising collateral and for processing our outgoing mail. We also work with companies that may provide investment services, financial planning, extended automotive service contracts and automobile leasing, personal and property insurance, and credit counseling.
Fair and Accurate Credit Transactions Act: The Credit Union may report information about your account(s) to third parties such as credit reporting agencies/bureaus. Late payments, missed payments, insufficient funds transactions or other defaults on your loan and share/share draft account(s) may be reflected in your credit report.
We may also disclose non-public personal information about you to non-affiliated third parties as permitted by applicable law.
It is generally unnecessary for us to disclose information about former members of our credit union or others that have a relationship with us. However, to the extent we do disclose information; we will adhere to the same policies as described elsewhere in this notice .
Security. We are committed to taking every reasonable precaution to protect individual identifying information that you provide to us. We restrict access of non-public personal information about you to employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We also maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your non-public personal information.
Notices and "Joint Relationships." Except where expressly required by applicable law, we will provide all notices to the person (member) listed first on any application, agreement or other relevant document with us. The notice will be mailed to the address noted for said person on the application, agreement or other document. If this person (member) has agreed to receive notices and disclosures electronically, then we can send all such notices and notifications, to the e-mail or Internet address provided by said person. All joint owners, borrowers and guarantors agree to the receipt and sufficiency of any notice or notification sent according to this paragraph.
Modification. The Credit Union reserves the right to modify, change or amend this Member Privacy Policy and Agreement at any time without notice other than as expressly required by applicable law.
What members can do to help. Protect your account numbers, card numbers, PINs (personal identification numbers), and passwords. In particular, never keep your PIN with your debit card or credit card, as that makes you vulnerable in the event you lose your card or your card is stolen. Use caution in revealing account numbers, social security numbers, etc. to other persons. In particular, if a caller tells you he/she is calling you on behalf of the credit union and asks for your account number, you should beware. Legitimate credit union staff would already have access to that information. It’s important that the credit union has current information about how to reach you. If we detect potentially fraudulent use of your account, we will attempt to contact you immediately. If your address or phone number changes, please let us know.
Protecting Children. We do not knowingly solicit or collect data from children and we do not knowingly market to children online. We recognize that protecting children’s identities and online privacy is important and that responsibility rests with us and with parents.
Building Relationships to Provide Lifetime Financial Solutions.
Copyright © 2019. All rights reserved.
Routing No. 304982468 | NMLS #445421 | (402) 465-1000 | Toll Free: 1-855-501-4600
Top
():
